themavenreport.com 2010-05-10

# Privacy Policy | The Maven Report

**Privacy Policy**

At The Maven Report™, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our users and visitors.  The following Privacy Policy outlines the information Ichibon Media Group, Inc. (“Ichibon Media Group”) may collect and how we may use that information to better serve visitors and members of The Maven Report.  
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@themavenreport.com.

**1.   Children Under the Age of 13**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Ichibon Media Group does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the The Maven Report from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the The Maven Report at any time or in any manner. If Ichibon Media Group learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on The Maven Report without verified parental consent, then Ichibon Media Group will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

**2.   Information We Collect**

*  Information Submitted by a user.  Ichibon Media Group collects personal information when you register or request information from us. The personal information we collect is listed below:

•    Login Name  
•    Password  
•    Email address  
•    Name  
•    Postal Code  
•    Instant Messenger User Names (for example AIM, Yahoo, MSN)  
•    Personal Preferences (Favorite Colors, Style Description)  
•    Email address

* You may also submit information about other people. For example, you may enter a friend’s email to invite to The Maven Report, or email links to The Maven Report. In this circumstance, we collect the following information about the recipient:

* Non-submitted Information Collected.  Ichibon Media Group may also collect non-personal information not associated with your identity. We collect this data to improve The Maven Report. The non-submitted information we collect is listed below:

•    IP  
•   Time  
•   File  
•   Data transferred  
•   Browser type and version  
•   Operating system  
•   Cookies

**3.   How We Use Your Information**

Among our primary goals in collecting information is to provide you with a customized experience when visiting our site and to make our site more valuable to you.   We use this information to closely monitor which areas of the site are used most and to determine which areas we need to focus on improving. This information is used exclusively by The Maven Report™ in aggregate form so that we may continue to improve the value of the services and information on The Maven Report for our members as a whole.  
As a valued customer of Ichibon Media Group, we will occasionally contact you, typically by e-mail (or any other way you prefer) in order to notify you of special promotions, and up-to-date news, custom-tailored to your personal interests. Of course, if you do not wish to receive this personalized information, you can remove yourself from receiving such information by changing the appropriate option on your user account.  
Ichibon Media Group uses your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help diagnose problems with our computer server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you, and to gather broad demographic data. Your IP address contains no personal information about you.

Please note that, once you’ve logged on to our servers, we use cookies keep track of your application states and log in status. Cookies are small files that take up minimal room on your computer and cannot, by itself, damage your computer’s files.  Cookies work by assigning a number to a user that has no meaning outside of the assigning web site, in this case, The Maven Report.  If you do not want information to be collected through the use of cookies, your browser allows you to deny or accept the use of cookies.  There may, however, be some features on The Maven Report™ which requires the use of cookies in order to customize the delivery of information and content to you.

Except as described above, we will not monitor, edit or disclose any personal information about you or your account, without your prior consent unless we have a belief that such action is necessary to: (i) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Ichibon Media Group; (iii) enforce our Terms of Service; (iv) protect the interests of users of our services other than you or any other person; or (v) operate or conduct maintenance and repair of Ichibon Media Group’s services or equipment as authorized by law.

**4.   Our Disclosure of Your Information **

Ichibon Media Group does not sell or rent personal information about its customers to any third parties at this time.  In the event Ichibon Media Group does engage in such commerce in the future, you will have an opportunity to remove yourself from any such lists prior to your inclusion therein by emailing us at info@themavenreport.com or by changing the appropriate option on your user account. Ichibon Media Group does, however, perform statistical analysis of customer usage in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various parts of The Maven Report, and Ichibon Media Group shares that information with current and prospective advertisers, and other interested third parties. But, this information is aggregated data only (statistics, etc.), and contains no personally identifiable information whatsoever.

Ichibon Media Group cooperates with all law enforcement inquires and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights.

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas, on bulletin boards, or in classified areas within The Maven Report™, that information might be collected and disseminated by third-parties, and result in, among other things, unsolicited inquiries, messages, and offers from third-parties. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and this third-party conduct is out of the control of Ichibon Media Group. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

The Maven Report also contains links to other web sites. Ichibon Media Group is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. ****

**5.   Security**

The personally identifiable information we collect is securely stored within our database, and we use standard, industry-wide practices such as encryption, firewalls and (in some certain areas) SSL (Secure Socket Layers) for protecting your information. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. We recommend that you not disclose your password to anyone.

**6.   Revisions and Amendments**

If you have further privacy concerns please do not hesitate to ask us by contacting info@themavenreport.com. This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 19, 2007.  This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.  Ichibon Media Group reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, modify, change or update this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on www.themavenreport.com.  Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on The Maven Report.
